<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hiddenbyte.log</title><link>https://mehul.pt/</link><description>Recent content on hiddenbyte.log</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:03:55 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mehul.pt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CV - Mehul Irá</title><link>https://mehul.pt/docs/cv/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:03:55 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mehul.pt/docs/cv/</guid><description>Curriculum Vitae Personal information Full name: Mehul Sasikante Irá
E-mail: mehulira@protonmail.com
Work Experience Software Enginner at Mindera Since January 2022. Currently here.
Technologies: Java, Spring Framework and Elasticsearch.
Software Enginner at Sky Technology Centre - Portugal From May 2021 to December 2021.
Technologies: Kotlin, Spring Framework, Spring Boot and Couchbase.
Software Enginner at Mindera From August 2015 to May 2021.
Worked with several tech partners and/or clients, as a Software Developer, helping them build backend solutions for the Retail, Gambling, Gaming and SaaS business sectors.</description></item><item><title>Digging into Goroutines I</title><link>https://mehul.pt/posts/digging-into-goroutines-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 23:34:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mehul.pt/posts/digging-into-goroutines-1/</guid><description>Go enables writing programs with concurrent threads of execution. And it does so by introducing the concept of goroutine.
A goroutine has a simple model: it is a function executing concurrently with other goroutines in the same address space.
in Effective Go
Before digging into goroutines, having an understanding on &amp;ldquo;how&amp;rdquo; the Go compiler and runtime work together in order to launch a goroutine will pave the path to its internals.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://mehul.pt/pages/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 14:13:55 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mehul.pt/pages/about/</guid><description>Mehul Irá, Software Developer. For more details: Curriculum Vitae.
You can also find me at:
https://github.com/hiddenbyte https://twitter.com/hiddenbyte https://www.linkedin.com/in/mehulira About hiddenbyte.log Most of the log entries will be about Software Development.</description></item></channel></rss>